https://www.semcomotion.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement - Sign and Display Turntables
Semco Motion Products / Larsen Mfg.                        +1 801-876-2111
Privacy Statement
Larsen Manufacturing Company / Semco Revolving Units (SRU) respects the privacy of persons who visit our Web site.We do not sell or otherwise disclose any personal information regarding our Web site visitors to othercompanies or entities for marketing purposes.Collection of information from our visitors.Information we receive from our customers on our web site is comes from our Contact Us page form where customers provide us with their company name and email address. We use this information to contact people interested in knowing more about our product line and to provide them with the information they request.Credit Card information via telephone or fax is only shared with parties related to credit card processing. This includes secure servers, our credit card processing company, and banking companies related to the different credit cards used. It is our policy that your information is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide to us is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information. We will not sell any personal information you provide to us to another entity. We may disclose certain information to comply with a court order or if we have a good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to identify persons violating the law.Our web site is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not email addresses. For example, we can tell which internet service provider our visitors use, but no the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our site.Links to third party sites. Our web site may provide links to third party sites as a convenience to you. A third-party site may have its own privacy policy, which may differ from the policy expressed herein. Larsen Manufacturing Company does not control third party sites of the accuracy of links to third party sites. Larsen Manufacturing Company is not responsible for the contend of any linked sites. Links to third party sites are not endorsements by Larsen Manufacturing Company of such sites.
Products
Pricing
Semco Products
OEM Manufacturing
Services
Machining Line Card
Installation Ideas
Rotator size calculator
Semco Motion Products4116 W 5800 NMountain Green, UT 84050801-876-2111, email: sales@semcomotion.com
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Instagram
Copy Right © SRU inc / Semco Motion Products 2020. All rights reserved
